When there's a profound transformation of the system,
当系统发生深刻转变时，
you arrive, and then suddenly something changes.
你来了，然后突然间有些东西改变了。
A trance formation.
一种恍惚的形成。
You change your form again.
你改变了你的形态。
It's like an alchemical level that happens.
这就像一个炼金术的层面，就这样发生了。
There, there can be an energetic tissue change
在那里，可能会发生能量的组织变化，
where you get back on the wave of life's impermanence.
你重新回到生命无常的波浪上。
Energy 1 is there and I suddenly switch to energy 2.
能量1在那里，我突然进入能量2。
There is a transformation.
有一个转变。
And at that moment, there is a somewhat chaotic level here, where the person
在那一刻，这里有一个有点混乱的层面，在那里，这个人
can find
可能会发现
a moment of isolation.
一个孤立的时刻。
Sometimes you just have to be there, the word, you have to be careful that it's not
有时只需要在那里，言语，我们必须小心，不要
words, the gesture and also the gaze, which must have a
言语、姿态和眼神，都必须具有
liberating level.
解放的层面。
I bring them back into the trust of life, sometimes
我让他们重新信任生命，有时
which even goes beyond life.
甚至超越生命。
life and death. It is an act of presence. And this presence,
生命与死亡。这是一种临在的行为。而这种临在，
it is being present here
就是此刻
and now. It is in listening. It is returning to this state of freedom. And
的临在。它在于倾听。它在于回到那种自由的状态。而且
it is
在这种状态下做出决定是
good to decide in that state. You no longer have brakes because you are
很好的。你不再有束缚，因为你处于
in the movement
生命的
of life. The movement of life only happens in the gift of the present. But
运动中。生命的运动只发生在当下的馈赠中。但是
most
大多数
of the time, since we haven't understood our emotional context, we are in a system
时候，由于我们不理解自己的情感背景，我们处于一个系统中。
So we are not free, meaning I give the other the power to decide my life system.
所以我们不自由，也就是说，我把决定我生命系统的权力交给了别人。
There is a vertebra called the axis, and by chance, it has a small
有一块椎骨叫做枢椎，巧合的是，它有一个小小的
tooth, the odontoid process,
齿突，
which even has a silver thread, and that's why it's the second cervical vertebra.
甚至有一根银线穿过，这就是为什么它是第二颈椎。
And in the deep vision, it will connect you beyond your egoistic intelligence.
在深层视觉中，它将把你连接到超越你自私的智慧。
There is an important level that will connect...
有一个重要的层面将是连接...
second cervical vertebra, with your pineal and pituitary glands, and
第二颈椎，与你的松果体和垂体，并
give it back into a
将其重新置于一个
higher monad to you, which is a monad where you rejoin atma, manas
超越你的更高单子中，这是一个你重新连接阿特曼、摩那斯
and buddhi.
和菩提的单子。
That means you will rejoin love, wisdom and divine will.
这意味着你将重新连接爱、智慧和神圣意志。
And you will integrate an image in the form of a photonic plane to give it back to
你将以光子平面的形式整合一个图像，并将其重新投射到
the level
需要解放的
of psychic centers that need to be liberated.
精神中心层面。
This is a bit initiatory.
这有点像是入门。
This is where you will connect with levels that are already present, but of which you may not be
在这里，你将连接到那些已经存在但你可能没有
aware.
意识到的层面。
This means that we will be on the axis and we will see how ultimately the process
这意味着我们将处于轴线上，我们将看到中枢神经系统
neuro-gordal is influenced in its development by the external field.
在发展过程中如何受到外部场的影响。
That is to say, it is the environment that will give rise to creation.
也就是说，是环境促成了创造。
So the form is dependent on the outside.
因此，形式取决于外部。
trophic plane. I feed
营养层面。我从
from the universe.
宇宙中汲取营养。
By land, by sea, by land-sea.
通过大地，通过海洋，通过海陆。
The sphenobasilar synchondrosis,
蝶枕结合，
ultimately, is also
最终，也是
a reflection of occlusion.
咬合的反映。
The type of occlusion will have an impact
咬合类型会影响
on my synchondrosis, because
我的蝶枕结合，因为
the body, here, at the level
身体，在这里，在
of my teeth, I can take the constraints,
我的牙齿层面，我可以承受压力，
in fact. It's the densest
事实上。这是你身体
part of your body.
最致密的部分。
So that's what takes your frustrations.
所以它承受着你的烦恼。
You will always, as best you can, try to...
你总是会尽力去寻找...
have the best mobility.
获得最佳的活动性。
Unfortunately, at the level of dentists,
不幸的是，在牙医那里，
there is no such awareness.
没有这种意识。
Because as soon as I change an amalgam
因为一旦我更换一个汞合金
or put something in,
或放置一些东西，
I change a very deep structure.
我就改变了一个非常深层的结构。
And we will see that by the principle of the notochord
我们将看到，通过脊索的原理
and the base of the skull,
和颅底，
it is an integration on the overall posture of the body.
这是身体整体姿势的整合。
We could say that the teeth,
我们可以说牙齿，
are posture sensors.
它们是姿势感受器。
They are connected to every organ and every tissue.
它们与每个器官和每个组织相连。
And it's connected...
并且它与...
the deep chain. This means that a modification can have repercussions
深层链相连。这意味着一个改变可能会影响
in the globality
你姿势的
of your posture. But there is always a very important response that will occur
整体性。但总会有一个非常重要的反应发生
at the level
在
of the pituitary gland in relation to the hypothalamus, which
垂体层面，与下丘脑相关，
will also receive the integrity
下丘脑也会接收到完整性
of your acid-base system. So ultimately, it's a chemical tone in
你的酸碱系统。所以最终，它是一种化学张力，
relation to a
与一个
I always try to rebalance myself through movement.
我总是试图通过运动来重新平衡自己。
I always try, in relation to my environment, to have the best possible articulation.
我总是试图在我的环境中获得最佳的关节活动度。
That's why, for example, the alveoli are only the concentration of a global state
这就是为什么，例如，肺泡只是你呼吸整体状态的集中体现，
of your breathing,
你的呼吸，
on an acid-base level.
在酸碱平衡方面。
So every time I breathe, I will directly modify my balance.
所以每次我呼吸时，我都会直接改变我的平衡。
I stabilize myself.
我稳定下来。
Then I have another more important structure, which is the renal level.
然后我还有另一个更重要的结构，那就是肾脏层面。
with the redox system and the balance system, if you will,
与氧化还原系统和平衡系统，如果你愿意的话，
where I will have my excess bases, you see, that seek to balance themselves.
我会有我的过量碱基，你看，它们正在寻求平衡。
But it's longer, whereas the respiratory system is a rapid adaptation.
但这需要更长的时间，而呼吸系统是一种快速适应。
With each breath, you will redo this integration.
每一次呼吸，你都会重新进行这种整合。
It's a globality in its system.
这是一个系统中的整体性。
The expression of your posture, the expression of your face,
你的姿势表达，你面部的表达，
is the expression of your best possible adaptation of the moment.
是你当下最佳适应的表达。
A diagram of my sphenobasilar synchondrosis on a symbolic level.
我的蝶枕结合在象征层面上的图示。
I see that it's again like a symbol like this.
我看到它又像一个这样的符号。
And man, he finds himself like that.
而人，他就是这样。
Your digestive system, it finds itself like that.
你的消化系统，它就是这样。
Your base of the skull, it finds itself like that.
你的颅底，它就是这样。
You place your duodenum deep with the facial pentagon of the pancreas.
你将十二指肠深置于胰腺的面部五边形中。
This is my skull base here.
这是我的颅底。
And it receives information both visceral from top to bottom,
它同时接收来自上到下的内脏信息，
neuronal upwards,
神经向上，
but also all the tension membranes of the dural sheaths
但也包括硬膜鞘的所有张力膜
will have an impact here.
都会在这里产生影响。
We will see how my entire facial system,
我们将看到我的整个面部系统，
will also have repercussions on my skull base.
也会影响我的颅底。
This means that it is informed on a membranous level,
这意味着它在膜层面上被告知，
it is informed on a vascular level,
它在血管层面上被告知，
I have a huge pentagon,
我有一个巨大的五边形，
called the Circle of Willis which integrates here,
我们称之为Willis环，它在这里整合，
I have neurological information,
我有神经信息，
I have endocrine information,
我有内分泌信息，
it is completely informed of all the tissue quality of your system.
它完全被告知你系统所有组织的质量。
Now we know there's a lymphatic plane.
现在我们知道有一个淋巴平面。
It's really a place that knows everything.
这真是一个无所不知的地方。
and which constantly seeks, and it is the embryonic fixed point.
并且不断地寻求，这就是胚胎固定点。
This means that it is the point that can always receive all the information
这意味着这个点可以随时接收所有信息
and give you, if you give back silence, there is reorganization in
并给予你，如果你重新给予寂静，就会在
the still point
静止点
coming from the depth of your emptiness, which can restore health.
从你虚空的深处，它可以重新给予健康。